LEONARD:
How so?
SHELDON:
It has been some time...
(Sheldon:)...since we've had a woman
take her clothes off in our apartment.
(Sheldon:)That's not true.
Remember at Thanksgiving...
(Leonard:)...my grandmother with Alzheimer's
had that episode?
(Sheldon:)Point taken. It has been some time since
we've had a woman take her clothes off...
(Sheldon:)...after which
we didn't wanna rip our eyes out.
(Leonard:)The worst part
was watching her carve that turkey.
(Sheldon:)So, what exactly
are you trying to accomplish here?
(Leonard:)Excuse me?
(Sheldon:)That woman in there
is not going to have sex with you.
(Leonard:)Well, I'm not trying to have sex with her.
(Sheldon:)Oh, good.
Then you won't be disappointed.
(Leonard:)What makes you think
she wouldn't have sex with me?
(Leonard:)I'm a male and she's a female.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but not of the same species.
I'm not gonna engage
in hypotheticals here.
- I'm just trying to be a good neighbor.
- Oh, of course.
(Leonard:)That's not to say that
if a carnal relationship were to develop...
(Leonard:)...that I wouldn't participate.